<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about_app"><![CDATA["<p>Flóramo is a field guide to identify 100 species of wild plants found in the páramo, a vegetation type at the top of the Andes Mountains of tropical South America. It contains field images, species descriptions, and an identification key using life forms, flower colors or scientific names. A map with location of species, routes for personalized records. Additional features include searches into the Missouri Botanical Garden Tropicos® database. Flóramo currently includes plants found the in the Cajas massif of southern Ecuador, but various species are found beyond this area.</p><p>The Flora of Cajas project is a collaboration between the <a href='link::http://www.missouribotanicalgarden.org/'>Missouri Botanical Garden</a> and the <a href='link::http://www.uazuay.edu.ec/HerbarioAzuay/'>Azuay Herbarium</a> (Universidad del Azuay, Cuenca Ecuador) with Parque Nacional Cajas.</p><p>We thank the Prometeo program of Ecuador´s Secretaría de Educación Superior, Ciencia, Tecnología e Innovación for a research fellowship to Carmen Ulloa at Universidad del Azuay; to Etapa-Parque Nacional Cajas, Ministerio del Ambiente de Ecuador, and funding agencies for field work; to the National Geographic Society.</p><br/><p>Project contact: <a href='mailto::carmen.ulloa@mobot.org'>C. Ulloa</a></p><br/><p>All rights reserved.</p><p>©Missouri Botanical Garden, Science and Conservation Division</p>"]]></string>
    <string name="about_cajas"><![CDATA["<p>The Cajas massif is located 30 km west of the city of Cuenca, Azuay province in southern Ecuador. It is dominated by herbaceous páramo with scattered patches of forest.</p><p>Pleistocene glaciers carved the landscape resulting in a unique area of irregular topography with more than 235 lakes and lagoons and unparalleled scenic beauty. The climate is cold and humid; there is however, considerable daily weather variation that can change rapidly from calm to strong winds, from cloudy to intense sun, from dry to fog or drizzle, and from hard rain to hail. The minimum daily temperature is –2°C and the maximum is 18°C. The annual mean precipitation is 1200 mm. It has two access roads: the main Cuenca-Molleturo-Naranjal road, and the unpaved Cuenca-Soldados. The Área de Recreación Cajas was created in 1977 and upgraded to Cajas National Park in 1996.  It comprises 28,544 hectares, between 3150 and 4450 m asl.</p><br/><p>Read more: <a href='link::http://www.mobot.org/MOBOT/research/paramo/study.shtml'>Study area: Cajas National Park</a></p>"]]></string>
    <string name="about_contact">Contact us</string>
    <string name="about_paramo"><![CDATA["<p>Páramo is a unique mountain ecosystem dominated by bunch–grasses. It is found above the tree line and up to the permanent snow line (3000–5000 m/9000–15000 ft elev.) from Venezuela to northern Peru and on mountains in Panama and Costa Rica. The word páramo is associated to treeless inhospitable plains. However, páramos have high biological diversity and endemism, and constitute a unique biota.</p><p>Plants have adapted to the cold conditions, extreme solar irradiation, low atmospheric pressure, dramatic daily fluctuations in temperature, and seasonal rains. Many plants grow very close to the ground, forming <a href='info::rosette'>rosettes</a> and <a href='info::cushion'>cushion-plants</a>, or have reduced <a href='info::leaves'>hard leaves</a> or are covered with a dense layer of <a href='info::hairs'>white or silvery hairs</a>.</p><p>Páramos along with the Andean forests, function as a buffer in the hydrological cycle, which slowly releases the fallen rain water to rivers and lakes. The water captured in the páramos benefits millions of people that use it for consumption and irrigation.</p><p>The effect of the increase in temperatures due to climate change is already observed in peaks on the higher tropical mountains with a marked glacier retreat. Changes in the páramos hydrological cycle can bring catastrophic consequences and immense economic implications for the Andean countries that depend on this ecosystem for provision of water for human consumption, for operation of hydro-electrical plants, irrigation systems.</p><br/><p>Read more: <a href='link::http://www.mobot.org/MOBOT/Research/paramo_flora.shtml'>Páramo flora project</a></p>"]]></string>
    <string name="about_quito"><![CDATA["<p>The Metropolitan District of Quito (DMQ) is located in the Northern center of the province of Pichincha, Ecuador. Its irregular topography is crossed by several rivers that converge in two sub-basins, of the rivers Guayllabamba and Blanco. Its extension is 4,232 km2. The altitude ranges from 500 to 4,750 m. It includes multiple geomorphological and climate units, and vegetation formations. Its landscape is heterogeneous, influenced by its position in the Andean alley, and extending towards the slopes of the Western and Oriental Cordilleras of the Andes, that has resulted in the formation of various ecosystems with different vegetal and faunal composition. Vegetation cover consists of páramo, natural forest, forest with crops and pastureland, pastures, crops of short cycle and dry scrub.</p><p>The Páramos cover 11% and are located in the two mountain ranges of the Andes in areas with altitudes above 3,500 m. Frequent fires of anthropogenic origin have changed the composition and structure of its ecosystems. Despite the importance of the Páramo ecosystems as water sources of the DMQ that feed the hydrographic system and provide drinking water and irrigation to the rural and urban areas -like other páramos in the country- they are permanently facing activities harmful to their welfare and conservation, the burning of the grasslands, overgrazing and the expansion of agricultural frontier are among the most common activities. In the páramos of the DMQ, especially of the Guagua and Ruco Pichincha, Padre Encantado, Atacazo, Sincholagua, Pambamarca, Cerro Puntas, and Mojanda, each summer and even in winter, grasses are burned in order to obtain tender shoots for cattleand sheep. This activity has caused the reduction of the original vegetation cover that triggers strong erosion by wind and rain, in addition, many lakes and water sheds have dried and disappeared, in the absence of vegetation and due to livestock trampling. Probably these activities have been practiced for tens or hundreds of years and consequently, in the majority of páramos the original vegetation is gone, quite noticeable at Puntas, Pambamarca,and Sincholagua.</p><p>Six ecosystems are recognized in the DMQ páramos (MAE, 2013): <em>Arbustal siempreverde y Herbazal del Páramo, Bosque siempreverde del Páramo, Herbazal del Páramo,  Herbazal húmedo subnival del Páramo, Herbazal inundable del Páramo, y Herbazal y Arbustal siempreverde subnival</em>."]]></string>

    <string name="action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="action_sort_family">Sort by family</string>
    <string name="action_sort_name">Sort by name</string>

    <string name="android_version">Android version %1$s, SDK %2$s</string>

    <string name="appInfo_contact_mail" translatable="false">nth.development@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="appInfo_floraBase" translatable="false">http://www.mobot.org/MOBOT/paramo/search_paramo.asp?searchFor=</string>
    <string name="appInfo_folder_name" translatable="false">Floramo</string>
    <string name="appInfo_tropicos_api_key" translatable="false">34a6225b-552c-4e0b-9937-fe12a2541176</string>
    <string name="appInfo_tropicos_base_url" translatable="false">http://www.tropicos.org/Name/</string>
    <string name="appInfo_tropicos_max_results" translatable="false">100</string>
    <string name="appInfo_tropicos_url" translatable="false">http://services.tropicos.org/Name/Search</string>

    <string name="app_name">Flóramo</string>
    <string name="app_name_drawer">Flóramo</string>
    <string name="app_version">App version %1$s</string>

    <string name="cl_blue">Blue</string>
    <string name="cl_brown">Brown</string>
    <string name="cl_cone">Fern/Other</string>
    <string name="cl_green">Green</string>
    <string name="cl_none">-None-</string>
    <string name="cl_orange">Orange</string>
    <string name="cl_pink">Pink</string>
    <string name="cl_purple">Purple</string>
    <string name="cl_red">Red</string>
    <string name="cl_white">White</string>
    <string name="cl_yellow">Yellow</string>

    <string name="credits"><![CDATA["<p>The Cajas Flora project is a collaboration between the Missouri Botanical Garden and the Azuay Herbarium (Universidad del Azuay) with Parque Nacional Cajas.</p><p><b>Project contact</b></p><p><a href='mailto::carmen.ulloa@mobot.org'>C. Ulloa</a></p><br/><p><b>Design and development</b></p><p>L.M. Unda, V. Zapata, Quito, Ecuador</p><br/><p><b>Authors Cajas text</b></p><p>C. Ulloa Ulloa, D. Minga, R. Ansaloni, A. Verdugo, S. Álvarez, P. M. Jørgensen.</p><p><b>Authors DMQ text</b></p><p>B. Cuamacás, D. Fernández, E. Freire, M. Haro, V. Herrera, B. Obando, W. Palacios, M. Peñafiel, E. Rea, C. Ulloa Ulloa, M. Unda, A. Yánez.</p><p><b>Photographic credits</b></p><p>C. Aedo, D. Fernández, FloraoftheWorld.org, E. Freire, P. M. Jørgensen, P. Mena Vásconez, D. Minga, B. Obando, W. Palacios, C. Ulloa Ulloa, A. Verdugo.</p><p><b>Acknowledgments</b></p><p>We thank the support of the Prometeo program of Ecuador’s Secretaría de Educación Superior, Ciencia, Tecnología e Innovación for a fellowship to C. Ulloa Ulloa, Ph.D. at Ecuador’ National Herbarium of the National Institute of Biodiversity and at the Herbarium of Universidad del Azuay. To the Ministerio del Ambiente del Ecuador and Province offices, the project Mapa de Vegetación del Ecuador, Etapa-Parque Nacional Cajas, F. Sornoza (Yanacocha), Agua Potable del DMQ, the National Geographic. To S. Christoph y C. Davidson of FloraoftheWorld.org. M. Unda help updating data.</p><p><b>Icons</b></p><p><a href='link::http://www.freevectorvip.com/silhouette-of-tree-of-flowers-and-plants.html'>'Silhouette of tree of flowers and plants'</a>, licenced under Non commercial use, learning and reference use only.</p><p><a href='link::http://www.freevectorvip.com/marine-biology-silhouette.html'>'Marine biology silhouette'</a>, licenced under Non commercial use, learning and reference use only.</p><p><a href='link::https://design.google.com/icons/'>Material icons</a>, licenced under <a href='link::http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0'>Apache License Version 2.0</a></p><br/><p><b>Components</b></p><p><a href='link::https://github.com/woozzu/IndexableListView'>IndexableListView</a>, by Woozzu, licenced under <a href='link::http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0'>Apache License Version 2.0</a></p><p><a href='link::https://github.com/bieliaievays/ViewPagerIndicatorCircles'>ViewPagerIndicatorCircles</a>, by Iuliia Ashomok, licenced under <a href='link::http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0'>Apache License Version 2.0</a></p><p><a href='link::https://nishantvnair.wordpress.com/2010/09/28/flowlayout-in-android/'>FlowLayout</a>, by Nishant Nair</p><p><a href='link::http://www.androidhive.info/2013/09/android-fullscreen-image-slider-with-swipe-and-pinch-zoom-gestures/'>Android Fullscreen Image Slider with Swipe and Pinch Zoom Gestures</a>, by Ravi Tamada</p><p><a href='link::https://github.com/MikeOrtiz/TouchImageView'>TouchImageView</a>, by Mike Ortiz</p><br/><p>All rights reserved.</p><p>©Missouri Botanical Garden, Science and Conservation Division</p>"]]></string>

    <string name="detail_color">Color</string>
    <string name="detail_family">Family</string>
    <string name="detail_genus">Genus</string>
    <string name="detail_life_form">Life form</string>
    <string name="detail_species">Species</string>

    <string name="dialog_button_close">Close</string>

    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation menu</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation menu</string>

    <string name="fv_aquatic">Aquatic</string>
    <string name="fv_cushion">Cushion</string>
    <string name="fv_grass">Grass</string>
    <string name="fv_herb">Herb</string>
    <string name="fv_liana">Liana</string>
    <string name="fv_none">-None-</string>
    <string name="fv_rosette">Rosette</string>
    <string name="fv_shrub">Shrub</string>
    <string name="fv_tree">Tree</string>

    <string name="global_close">Close</string>

    <string name="help_card_title">App, Android and device information</string>
    <string name="help_comments">Comments, suggestions, feedback, bugs</string>
    <string name="help_comments_error">Please enter some text</string>
    <string name="help_subject">Comments, suggestions, feedback, bugs</string>

    <string name="loading_message">Please wait while we search</string>
    <string name="loading_title">Loading</string>

    <string name="menu_about">About this app</string>
    <string name="menu_about_cajas">Cajas</string>
    <string name="menu_about_dmq">DMQ</string>
    <string name="menu_about_paramo">Páramo</string>
    <string name="menu_about_this_app">This app</string>
    <string name="menu_credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="menu_encyclopedia">Encyclopedia</string>
    <string name="menu_group_about">About</string>
    <string name="menu_help">Bug reports, feedback</string>
    <string name="menu_search">Search</string>
    <string name="menu_title">Navigation</string>
    <string name="menu_tropicos">Tropicos® Search</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open</string>

    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="search_btn_label">Search</string>
    <string name="search_color_info">Species with color %1$s</string>
    <string name="search_conditional_info_and">Search species matching ALL of the next criteria:</string>
    <string name="search_conditional_info_or">Search species matching ANY of the next criteria:</string>
    <string name="search_life_form_info">Species with life form %1$s</string>
    <string name="search_no_results">No results match your search</string>
    <string name="search_radio_and">AND search</string>
    <string name="search_radio_or">OR search</string>
    <string name="search_text_info">Species with family, genus or name containing %1$s</string>
    <string name="search_txt_hint">Family, genus or species</string>

    <string name="title_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_about_app">App</string>
    <string name="title_about_cajas">Cajas</string>
    <string name="title_about_paramo">Páramo</string>
    <string name="title_about_quito">Quito</string>
    <string name="title_credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="title_detail">Flóramo</string>
    <string name="title_encyclopedia">Encyclopedia</string>
    <string name="title_feedback">Bug reports, feedback</string>
    <string name="title_search">Search</string>
    <string name="title_tropicos">Tropicos® Search</string>
    <string name="title_webview">Web view</string>

    <string name="tropicos_common_name">Common name</string>
    <string name="tropicos_family">Family</string>
    <string name="tropicos_info">Enter at least one of the following criteria to perform a search on the Tropicos® database. This search will show up to %1$s results.</string>
    <string name="tropicos_info_warning">This search will connect to the internet</string>
    <string name="tropicos_name">Name</string>
    <string name="tropicos_search_result_author">Author:</string>
    <string name="tropicos_search_warning">Enter at leat one criteria to perform the search</string>
</resources>
